const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Is skill development crucial for career growth?",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How can one start a career in IT?",
    answer: "Learn skills and gain experience",
    options: [
      "Focus on traditional careers",
      "Invest years and huge finances",
      "Learn skills and gain experience",
      "Rely on quick results"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A growth oriented career guarantees salary growth and ___ opportunities.",
    answer: "International",
    options: ["Local", "International", "Limited", "Temporary"]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> A recent graduate is considering a career in IT. They have a degree in mechanical engineering but are unsure about the transition. They are interested in roles like full stack developer or Al engineer.<br> <b> Identify the incorrect step for IT career transition.</b>`,
    answer: "Rely on degree alone",
    options: [
      "Dedicate 6-12 months",
      "Learn high-demand skills",
      "Rely on degree alone",
      "Gain real-world experience"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> An individual is deciding between pursuing a traditional career or entering the IT field. They have limited financial resources and are looking for a career with growth opportunities.<br> <b> Select best correct benefits of an IT career.</b> `,
    answer: "Lower financial investment and Requires long study years",
    options: [
      "Lower financial investment and Requires long study years",
      "Limited job roles",
      "High growth potential",
      "Requires long study years"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Do real-world projects enhance job readiness?",
    answer: "Correct",
    options: ["Incorrect","Correct"]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What defines a growth-oriented career?",
    answer: "Salary growth and job satisfaction",
    options: [
      "Salary growth and job satisfaction",
      "Parental pressure and wedding cards",
      "Quick results and shortcuts",
      "Low-paying and irrelevant jobs"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The key to career growth is developing___skills.",
    answer: "valuable",
    options: ["basic", "general", "common", "valuable"]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b>A student is planning their career path and is evaluating different fields. They are considering traditional careers like medicine and law, but are also interested in IT due to its growth potential.<br> <b>Identify the incorrect reason to choose IT.</b>`,
    answer:"Requires massive financial investment",
    options: [
      "Diverse job roles",
      "Requires massive financial investment",
      "High salary potential",
      "Shorter study duration"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> A young professional is seeking advice on how to enhance their career prospects. They are currently employed in a low-paying job unrelated to their field of study.<br> <b> Select best correct steps to improve career prospects.</b>`,
    answer:"Develop valuable skills and Gain real-world experience",
    options: [
      "Develop valuable skills and Gain real-world experience",
      "Avoid further education",
      "Gain real-world experience",
      "Stay in current job"
    ]
  }
];
